Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/rachel-tulin (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Wireshark

Python (Programming Language) Network Administration

Rachel Tulin

Studying Cybersecurity @ Fullstack Academy | Aspiring SOC Analyst | Problem Solver | Proprietor

New Orleans, Louisiana, United States

Summary

I have been self-employed for several years. I own and manage a couple of rental properties abroad, and I own a small Pharmacy in the Philippines, where I was born and raised. As much as I'm fond of managing several businesses online, I have always been interested in cyberspace and have a passion for information technology.

I am now studying Cybersecurity BootCamp at Fullstack Academy, where I'm currently learning its fundamentals, such as detecting threats and incident response, analyzing network systems using Wireshark and Python, bash scripting, and cryptography. After I graduate from this program, I will be looking for a role where I can apply my knowledge and skills in the cyber industry.

Experience

Happy Med Pharmacy (RQ Pharmacy) Owner May 2023 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Philippines

Happy Med Pharmacy is a franchise retail pharmacy that sells prescription and non-prescription medications to the general public. In addition to the medication, Happy Med Pharmacy also sells beauty and personal care products, nutritional supplements, and related devices.

- •Supervise team of pharmacy staff members.
- •Increase sales and customer satisfaction by optimizing the filling process to reduce wait times.
- •Promote pharmacy services to patients and medical providers.
- Manage inventory.
- •Ensure compliance with all applicable laws and regulations.

RQ Homes

Real Estate Rental Manager | Owner April 2019 - Present (5 years 11 months)

Philippines

- •Market rentals to grow reservations and supply ads with exceptional pictures and descriptions.
- •Maintain a calendar of reservations to prevent double-booking and view upcoming rentals.
- •Provides an exceptional guest experience from check-in until checkout.
- Airbnb: https://www.airbnb.com/users/show/132555354

United States Postal Service

Postal Worker

October 2020 - May 2021 (8 months)

Rhode Island, United States

- •Sort outgoing and/or incoming mail using automated equipment.
- •Ensure all necessary support equipment and materials are organized for sorting.
- •Provide services at public window for non-financial transactions.
- •Lifting or carrying moderate to heavy mail and packages.

Education

Fullstack Academy

Cybersecurity Bootcamp · (August 2023 - November 2023)

Blue Cliff College-Metairie

Certificate, Medical/Clinical Assistant · (January 2019 - October 2019)

ACLC College

Associate's Degree, Software Development · (May 2009 - July 2011)